as the price is going up in the stock
market volume is decreasing as you can
see here right you can see as the stock
market moves higher the volume is going
down so two bearish divergences here
Market's trying to go higher it's
getting weaker Market is trying to go
higher volume is decreasing and to top
it all off you have this special pattern
that I want to point out and maybe
special is the wrong word to use but you
have this right here okay so you have
top one into
top
two into an overshoot into top three
here right and so this right here is the
exact same pattern you're seeing happen
right now okay so take that there take
that
there and take that there same pattern
right